quire.io 2019-05-25

# Quire Privacy Policy

Last updated: January 15, 2018

Thanks for entrusting Potix Corporation, who creates and maintains Quire, with your tasks, your projects, and your personal information. Holding onto your private information is a serious responsibility, and we want you to know how we're handling it. 

## The short version

We collect your information only with your consent; we only collect the minimum amount of personal information that is necessary to fulfill the purpose of your interaction with us; we don't sell it to third parties; and we only use it as this Privacy Policy describes. Of course, the short version doesn't tell you everything, so please read on for more details! 

## What information Quire collects and why

### Information from website browsers

If you're **just browsing the website** , we collect the same basic information that most websites collect. We use common internet technologies, such as cookies and web server logs. This is stuff we collect from everybody, whether they have an account or not. 

The information we collect about all visitors to our website includes the visitor’s browser type, language preference, referring site, additional websites requested, and the date and time of each visitor request. We also collect potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. 

### Why do we collect this?

We collect this information to better understand how our website visitors use Quire, and to monitor and protect the security of the website. 

### Information from users with accounts

If you **create an account with email** , we will require some basic information at the time of account creation. You will create your own user name and password, and we will ask you for a valid email account. 

If you **create an account through Google sign in** , we will ask for permissions to view your Google account name, email and profile photo. You need to click Allow to allow Quire to use this information from Google to log in Quire. In addition, you have the option to authorize Quire to browse the files in your Google Drive. We only store the links to the files that you chose under your request, but we do not access their contents. Only people you have shared permissions with can access these chosen files from your Google Drive. 

You can give us more information if you want to, and this may include “User Personal Information." 

"User Personal Information" is any information about one of our users which could, alone or together with other information, personally identify him or her. Information such as a user name and password, an email address, a real name, and a photograph are examples of “User Personal Information.” 

User Personal Information does not include aggregated, non-personally identifying information. We may use aggregated, non-personally identifying information to operate, improve, and optimize our website and service. 

### Why do we collect this?

  * We need your User Personal Information to create your account, and to provide the services you request.
  * We use your User Personal Information, specifically your user name, to identify you on Quire.
  * We use it to fill out your profile and share that profile with other users if you ask us to.
  * We will use your email address to communicate with you, if you’ve subscribed to receive related notifications about Quire, and when necessary.
  * We limit our use of your User Personal Information to the purposes listed in this Privacy Policy.

## What information Quire does not collect

We do not intentionally collect **sensitive personal information** , such as social security numbers, genetic data, health information, or religious information. Although Quire does not request or intentionally collect any sensitive personal information, we realize that you might store this kind of information in your account, such as in a project or task. If you store any sensitive personal information on our servers, you are consenting to our storage of that information on our servers, which are in the United States. 

We do not intentionally collect information that is **stored in your projects** or other free-form content inputs. Information in your projects belongs to you, and you are responsible for it, as well as for making sure that your content complies with our Terms of Service. 

If your project is public, anyone (including us) may view its contents. If you have included private or sensitive information in your public project, such as email addresses, that information may be indexed by search engines or used by third parties. In addition, while we do not generally search for content in your projects, we may scan our servers for certain tokens or security signatures. 

If you're a **child under the age of 13** , you may not have an account on Quire. Quire does not knowingly collect information from or direct any of our content specifically to children under 13. If we learn or have reason to suspect that you are a user who is under the age of 13, we will unfortunately have to close your account. 

## How we share the information we collect

We **do not** share, sell, rent, or trade User Personal Information with third parties for their commercial purposes. 

We **do** share certain aggregated, non-personally identifying information with others about how our users, collectively, use Quire. However, we do not sell this information to advertisers or marketers. 

We may occasionally embed content from third party sites, such as YouTube, and that content may include ads. While we try to minimize the amount of ads our embedded content contains, we can't always control what third parties show. 

We may share User Personal Information with your permission, so we can perform services you have requested. 

We may share User Personal Information with a limited number of third-party vendors who process it on our behalf to provide or improve our service, and who have agreed to privacy restrictions similar to our own Privacy Policy. Our vendors perform services such as payment processing, customer support ticketing, network data transmission, and other similar services. 

We may share User Personal Information if we are involved in a merger, sale, or acquisition. If any such change of ownership happens, we will ensure that it is under terms that preserve the confidentiality of User Personal Information, and we will notify you on our website or by email before any transfer of your User Personal Information. The organization receiving any User Personal Information will have to honor any promises we have made in our Privacy Policy or in our Terms of Service. 

## Public Information on Quire

A few Quire projects are public-facing. If you make a project public-facing, third parties may access and use it in compliance with our Terms of Service. We do not sell that content; it is yours. 

Your Personal Information, associated with your content, may be gathered by third parties in these compilations of Quire data. If you do not want your Personal Information to appear in third parties’ compilations of Quire data, please do not make your Personal Information publicly available and be sure to configure your email address and basic profile information to be private in your Account Settings. 

Similarly, projects on Quire may include publicly available Personal Information collected as part of the collaborative process. In the event that a Quire project contains publicly available Personal Information that does not belong to Quire users, we will only use that Personal Information for the limited purpose for which it was collected, and we will secure that Personal Information as we would secure any User Personal Information. 

## Our use of cookies and tracking

### Cookies

Quire uses cookies to make interactions with our service easy and meaningful. We use cookies (and similar technologies, like HTML5 localStorage) to keep you logged in, remember your preferences, and provide information for future development of Quire. 

A cookie is a small piece of text that our web server stores on your computer or mobile device, which your browser sends to us when you return to our site. Cookies do not necessarily identify you if you are merely visiting Quire; however, a cookie may store a unique identifier for each logged in user. The cookies Quire sets are essential for the operation of the website, or are used for performance or functionality. By using our website, you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your computer or device. If you disable your browser or device’s ability to accept cookies, you will not be able to log in or use Quire’s services. 

### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics as a third party tracking service, but we don’t use it to track you individually or collect your User Personal Information. We use Google Analytics to collect information about how our website performs and how our users, in general, navigate through and use Quire. This helps us evaluate our users' use of Quire; compile statistical reports on activity; and improve our content and website performance. 

Google Analytics gathers certain simple, non-personally identifying information over time, such as your IP address, browser type, internet service provider, referring and exit pages, time stamp, and similar data about your use of Quire. We do not link this information to any of your personal information such as your user name. 

Quire will not, nor will we allow any third party to, use the Google Analytics tool to track our users individually; collect any User Personal Information other than IP address; or correlate your IP address with your identity. Google provides further information about its own privacy practices and offers a [browser add-on to opt out of Google Analytics tracking](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). 

Certain pages on our site may set other third-party cookies. For example, we may embed content, such as videos, from another site that sets a cookie. While we try to minimize these third party cookies, we can’t always control what cookies this third party content sets. 

## How Quire secures your information

Quire takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect User Personal Information from unauthorized access, alteration, or destruction; maintain data accuracy; and help ensure the appropriate use of User Personal Information. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. 

No method of transmission, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

## Quire's global privacy practices

**Information that we collect will be stored and processed** in the United States and Taiwan in accordance with this Privacy Policy. However, we understand that we have users from different countries and regions with different privacy expectations, and we try to meet those needs. 

We provide the same standard of privacy protection to all our users around the world, regardless of their country of origin or location, and we are proud of the levels of notice, choice, accountability, security, data integrity, access, and recourse we provide. We work hard to comply with the applicable data privacy laws wherever we do business. 

In particular:

  * Quire provides clear methods of unambiguous, informed consent at the time of data collection, when we do collect your personal data. 
  * We collect only the minimum amount of personal data necessary, unless you choose to provide more. We encourage you to only give us the amount of data you are comfortable sharing. 
  * We offer you simple methods of accessing, correcting, or deleting the data we have collected.
  * We provide our users notice, choice, accountability, security, and access, and we limit the purpose for processing.

## Resolving Complaints

If you have concerns about the way Quire is handling your User Personal Information, please let us know immediately. We want to help. You may email us directly at [support@quire.io](mailto:support@quire.io) with the subject line "Privacy Shield Concerns." 

## How we respond to compelled disclosure

Quire may disclose personally-identifying information or other information we collect about you to law enforcement in response to a valid subpoena, court order, warrant, or similar government order, or when we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect our property or rights, or those of third parties or the public at large. In complying with court orders and similar legal processes, Quire strives for transparency. When permitted, we will make a reasonable effort to notify users of any disclosure of their information, unless we are prohibited by law or court order from doing so, or in rare, exigent circumstances. 

## How you can access and control the information we collect

If you're already a Quire user, you may access, update, alter, or delete your basic user profile information by editing your user profile or contacting us at [support@quire.io](mailto:support@quire.io). 

### Data Retention and Deletion

Quire will retain User Personal Information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. 

We may retain certain User Personal Information indefinitely, unless you delete it or request its deletion. For example, we don’t automatically delete inactive user accounts, so unless you choose to delete your account, we will retain your account information indefinitely. 

If you would like to cancel your account or delete your User Personal Information, you may do so in your Account Setting. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements, but barring legal requirements, we will delete your full profile (within reason) within 30 days. 

## How we communicate with you

We will use your email address to communicate with you, if you’ve subscribed to receive related notifications about Quire, and when necessary. You have a lot of control over how your email address is used and shared on and through Quire. You may manage your communication preferences in your Account Setting. 

Depending on your email settings, Quire may occasionally send notification emails about new features, requests for feedback, important policy changes, or offer customer support. We also send marketing emails, but only with your consent. You can unsubscribe any time. 

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Quire may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will provide notification to Users of material changes to this Privacy Policy through our Website or sending email to the email address specified in your account. For changes to this Privacy Policy that do not affect your rights, we encourage visitors to check this page frequently. 

## Contacting Quire

Questions regarding Quire's Privacy Policy or information practices should be sent to [support@quire.io](mailto:support@quire.io).
